<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-07T22:17:26-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sarah June Fischer, LLC</title><subtitle>Hello! Thanks for visiting my portfolio. Together, we can make the web a better place.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Big, Grand Announcement: Part 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-big-grand-announcement-part-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Big, Grand Announcement: Part 1" /><published>2019-04-07T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-04-07T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/the-big-grand-announcement-part-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-big-grand-announcement-part-1">&lt;p&gt;“Tell me, what is it you plan to do with your one wild and precious life?” — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.habitsforwellbeing.com/what-will-you-do-with-your-one-wild-and-precious-life/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mary Oliver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some news! (If you’re in a rush, get the &lt;a href=&quot;#tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/a&gt; here.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ready?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I quit my job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Slightly panics *&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To clarify, I quit my job without having &lt;em&gt;another&lt;/em&gt; job. I’ll be honest, it’s not something I ever pictured myself doing. That would be &lt;em&gt;risky&lt;/em&gt;. And aren’t risk-takers those people who climb to really high places and then yell, “YOLO!” as they jump off? For &lt;em&gt;fun&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, it turns out that—according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/risk-taker&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Merriam-Webster&lt;/a&gt;—”risk-takers” are people who are “willing to do things that involve danger or risk in order to achieve a goal.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting and achieving a goal? Now &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; I can get behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;halfwidth&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/sign-me-up.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Sign Me Up&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;so-whats-the-goal&quot;&gt;So… What’s the goal?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this change is to blend the life I want to live with the work I love to do: designing &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; cool things while traveling to interesting places. This means focusing my career solely on design (instead of the mix of design and content creation I was doing before) and pursuing work that is location-independent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I didn’t feel I could properly make this change while still in a full-time job. There was a lot of time-intensive work ahead: redesigning my website (tada!), studying all of the tutorials and resources I’d been amassing, and seeking out roles that more closely align with my new goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I decided to do something risky: quit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, this decision didn’t come without a lot of prep and research. As I laid the groundwork, it was encouraging to see how many people and companies are building a culture to support completely distributed teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing about this change was another step I wanted to take (thanks for being a part of it!). Publicly shared goals can be very motivating, so here’s what I’ll be doing to turn this dream into a reality:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pursue excellence in design&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Say yes to unexpected opportunities and new places&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stretch the limits of my comfort zone&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Blog about what I’m learning through this process&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add new design skills to my wheelhouse (like motion graphics!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know exactly what the outcome of this change will look like. There may be an opportunity just around the corner, or I may have years of freelancing ahead of me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do know that I’m looking forward to teaming up with some amazing people, traveling to new places, and producing designs that are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NHHEcmZtJvY&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;really, really ridiculously good looking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;halfwidth&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/blue-steel.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Keep Your Eye on the Ball&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Blue Steel, anyone?&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;and-lastly-my-thank-you-speech&quot;&gt;And lastly, my thank-you speech…&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to say thank you to everyone I’ve had the pleasure of working with over the past five years. During that time, I went from copy editing blog articles as an intern to overseeing all content creation: the website, print material, guides, blog posts, student interviews, advertising creative, email content… the list goes on, and I couldn’t have asked for a better place to grow. I wouldn’t be able to start the next phase of my career without the experience, confidence, and relationships that I gained in the last half decade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also so grateful to the &lt;em&gt;many&lt;/em&gt; people who have been willing to answer my questions around freelancing, give design feedback, and share advice and encouragement. You know who you are and you have my sincerest gratitude.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thats-it&quot;&gt;That’s it!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for making it to the end of The Big, Grand Announcement: Part 1*! You’re the best. 😘&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Part 2 coming soon. Until then, please enjoy The Best Gif of All Time:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;halfwidth&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/the-best-gif.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Keep Your Eye on the Ball&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I quit my job as part designer, part jack-of-all-marketing-trades to focus my full energy on design. If you want to collaborate on a project (hire me!), &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarah@sarahjunefischer.com&quot;&gt;get in touch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sarah</name></author><summary type="html">“Tell me, what is it you plan to do with your one wild and precious life?” — Mary Oliver</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/announcement-part-1.jpg" /></entry></feed>